StephenBrady

Old Park · Bandon · Co. Cork · Ireland ⊠ stephen.mk.brady@gmail.com ☎ (083) 192-4882

Овјестіче

A qualified and experienced test engineer with 3 years commercial manual testing experience and almost 2 years automated testing via python test framework in the telecommunications industry. During this period I have also gained valuable experience in Agile development and waterfall SDLC's, and mentoring of others. With both technical and interpersonal skills, looking for a challenging and more technical role that utilises my some of my previous skills and experiences with an emphasis on programming.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Period	January 2013 — Present	
Employer	Pilz Ireland	Model Farm Rd. Cork, IE
Job Title	Software Test Engineer	
Technologies	61131 IL, STL, Ladder logic diagram, Java SE 7, Google windows tester,	
	HP ALM	

Worked closely with development and test teams, Project Managers, and Requirements Engineers. Carried out Functional, Non-Functional, Performance, Installation and GUI testing. Responsible for Software Test strategy and planning. Analyzed and reviewed Requirements and Use Cases. Reviewed Unit Test plans to increase Unit Test coverage. Produced and maintained Test documentation including Plans, Test Cases Test Results and Reports. Delivered Management and Team presentations in the areas of Test Strategies, Test progress, process improvements. Developed Test code (IEC 61131) and rewrote customer and developer test code to improve testability.

Period	September 2010 — June 2012
Employer	Tait Communications Christchurch, NZ
Job Title	R&D Test Engineer
Technologies	Python, Bash, Android Java, C#, WML, GPIB Agilent, Fitnesse, SQL,
	RS232, Cadsoft Eagle, P25/MPT/Analogue radio systems

It was my responsibility to design, develop and maintain radio feature regression tests written in python. It was also my responsibility to maintain and upgrade the physical test system while working within Agile Scrum teams. Other responsibilities included testing the PC application software. Manual Exploratory testing of radio and test tool hardware and Software Investigate and organise the hardening of RF immunity in the physical test system. Software and Hardware test tool development. Mentor Summer student to develop an Android application. Fitnesse Test Case development.

Period June 2010 — September 2010

Employer Enatel Ltd. Christchurch, NZ

Job Title Test Technician &Assembler

Technologies RS232, power hardware circuitry

Responsibilities included assembling rack mounted DC power systems. Building complete prototype/sample/one-off/first in production run systems to specification. Testing systems meticulously and diagnosing faults that occur. Repairing/reworking faulty or damaged parts or systems. Working with the production and design engineers to troubleshoot and solve production issues.

EDUCATION

Period	2006 - 2008	
Degree	Bachelor of Engineering(Hons.) Degree in Digital and Software Systems De-	
	sign	
University	Galway Mayo Institute of Technology	Galway, Ireland
Period	2003 — 2004	
Degree	Diploma in Electronic Engineering	
University	Galway Mayo Institute of Technology	Galway, Ireland
Period	2001 — 2003	
Degree	Certificate in Electronic Engineering	
University	Galway Mayo Institute of Technology	Galway, Ireland

Skills

Computer Languages	Java SE7, Python, Android Java, C#, 61131-3 IL, STL, LD, LETEX
Protocols & APIs	RS232, I ² C, TCPIP, P25, MPT, Analogue CTCSS & DCS
Databases	MySQL
Tools	SVN, Git, LAMP, JIRA, HP ALM, Rational Clearquest & DOORS